Farewell, Earth
The ship that is departing is
The Space Battleship
Yamato
It departs now to Iscandar,
at the end of the cosmos,
bearing its fate.
"We will come back, no matter what it takes"
Answer with a smile to the waving people
Going far from the Galaxy towards Iscandar
A faint gleam of hope
The Space Battleship Yamato
Pluto
<Reflecting satellite 4. Deploying reflector.>
<Correcting angle +5 degrees.>
<Reflecting satellite 8. Deploying reflector.>
<Correcting angle +4 degrees.>
<Recharging energy! Quickly!>
<40 seconds until energy charging complete.>
Directly Above
Episode 5
The Trap on All Sides
The unknown calls to us
Does your courage burn to go there?
We rush on a journey
For everyone to survive together
For happiness
Though there is pain
And sadness
We will not be defeated
Those who know the beautiful Earth
Restore its wonders
Bring it back, bring it back
The road to tomorrow
Not afraid anymore
Determined to reach our destination